<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<Showinfo> 
  <showid>25745</showid> 
  <showname>Better With You</showname> 
  <showlink>http://www.tvrage.com/Better_Together</showlink> 
  <seasons>1</seasons> 
  <image>http://images.tvrage.com/shows/26/25745.jpg</image> 
  <started>2010</started> 
  <startdate>Sep/22/2010</startdate> 
  <ended></ended> 
  <origin_country>US</origin_country> 
  <status>New Series</status> 
  <classification>Scripted</classification> 
  <summary>Which kind of love is better, the slow and steady kind that grows over time or the truly, madly deeply kind that happens in a flash? Two couples, from two different generations, have very different outlooks on love. But together, they discover that when it comes to relationships, everyone has to find their own way. Ben and Maddie followed every rule, except for getting married. After nine years together, they're totally committed to each other and they don't need a stupid piece of paper to prove it, thank you very much. At least until Maddie's little sister Mia gets engaged. Mia and Casey are completely different from Ben and Maddie. Young and impulsive, Mia and Casey live in the moment which might have something to do with how Mia and Casey ended up both pregnant and engaged after only two months of dating. At first, Ben and Maddie are shocked... and maybe even a little jealous. Should they have gotten married at some point? They're even more jealous when Maddie and Mia's notoriously high-maintenance, meddling parents, the Putneys, welcome their new son-in-law with open arms. Maddie and Ben have to ask themselves... is their slow, cautious love as strong as Mia and Casey's untamed version? As Ben and Maddie welcome Casey into their lives and help guide him through the minefields of Maddie and Mia's eccentric family little by little both of these couples discover that married or not, it's the togetherness that counts. From creator Shana Goldberg-Meehan (Friends, Mad About You) comes a fresh, funny look at couplehood. No two relationships are quite alike. That's part of what makes them so great.</summary>
  <genres>
    <genre>Comedy</genre>
    <genre>Family</genre>
  </genres> 
  <runtime>30</runtime> 
  <network country="US">ABC</network> 
  <airtime>20:30</airtime> 
  <airday>Wednesday</airday> 
  <timezone>GMT-5 -DST</timezone> 
  <akas>
    <aka attr="working title">Better Together</aka>
    <aka attr="Alternate title" country="US">Leapfrog</aka>
    <aka attr="Alternate title" country="US">That Couple</aka>
  </akas> 
</Showinfo>
